(Leonard:)...which clearly appears to be a previously
unknown state of matter.
[AUDIENCE APPLAUDING]
(Leonard:)Thank you.
- Are there any questions?
MAN: Yeah.
(Voice:)What the hell was that?
(Leonard:)Any other questions?
Dr. Sheldon Cooper here.
I am the lead author of this particular paper.
(Leonard:)Thank you.
(Sheldon(who previously spoke, now removing his hood and dark glasses):)And you, sir, you have completely
skipped over the part...
(Sheldon(who previously spoke, now removing his hood and dark glasses):)...where I was walking through
the park...
(Sheldon(who previously spoke, now removing his hood and dark glasses):)...and I saw these children
on a merry-go-round...
(Sheldon(who previously spoke, now removing his hood and dark glasses):)...which started me thinking
about the moment of inertia...
(Sheldon(who previously spoke, now removing his hood and dark glasses):)...in gasses like helium at temperatures
approaching absolute zero.
(Leonard:)I didn't skip it.
It's just an anecdote. It's not science.
Oh, I see. It was the apple falling
on Newton's head.
(Sheldon:)Was that just an anecdote?
- You are not Isaac Newton.
- No, no, that's true.
(Sheldon:)Gravity would have been apparent to me
without the apple.
You cannot be that arrogant.